(Sheldon:)In fact, I'm going to begin
preparing my defense right now.
(Howard:)Okay, he's going to jail.
(Leonard(after Raj whispers to him):)Oh, that's right.
Thursday's Stan Lee day.
(Sheldon:)Now you see what you've done?
(Sheldon:)Because of you,
we're all going to miss Stan Lee.
(Leonard:)Whoa!
-What do you mean "all"?
-Well, you're my friends.
(Sheldon:)You'll be standing by my side,
supporting me...
(Sheldon:)...feeding me legal precedents,
and, if you have the strength...
(Sheldon:)...carrying me out on your shoulders
when I'm victorious.
(Leonard:)Yeah, okay, no.
(Sheldon:)Are you saying that you will not stand
beside me as I plead my case?
(Leonard:)That's what I'm saying.
(Sheldon:)-Howard?
-Wow. Ahem.
(Howard:)Uh, Stan Lee or you in court.
(Howard:)Uh, if this was Sophie's Choice,
it would've been a much shorter movie. No.
Raj, you'll be there, won't you?